(Bernadette:)-How?
-In a bad way, very bad.
(Raj:)Hey, guys.
(Howard:)Whatever you hear tonight,
just remember I love you.
Hey!
(Raj:)Emily, these are my good
friends, Howard and Bernadette.
(Raj:)-Guys, this is Emily.
-Nice to meet you.
(Leonard:)-Hi.
-Hello.
(Emily:)Have we met before?
(Raj:)No.
(Leonard:)I don't. ..
I don't... think so.
(Emily:)You sure? You look familiar.
(Howard:)Well, you sure don't.
(Howard:)You I know,
you I know, you?
(Howard:)Total stranger.
(Howard:)Even if you had yummy candy,
I would not get in your van.
(Emily:)Did you go to that spin class
on Green Street?
(Howard:)That must be it.
(Raj:)Since when do you go to spin class?
(Howard:)Wow. Now who doesn't listen?
(Amy:)Sheldon, your food's getting cold.
What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Looking through my textbooks
for a new field of inquiry.